mediatoolbox-online.com 2013-08-21

# Media toolbox online - Page

This website (the "Site") and the services provided herein such as "Media Toolbox Online" (the **"Services"** ), as defined below, is made available to you by Roadpass Ltd ("Roadpass"). In this Privacy Policy we explain the type of information we collect through our Site, and Services, and what we do with such information.

This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms and conditions available at:

<http://www.mediatoolbox-online.com/page/disclaimer>

If you choose to enter our Site and use out Services you will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.

As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms: "the company", "we" and "us" refer to Roadpass Ltd. or any successor or assign of Roadpass Ltd.

### Privacy and use of information

Roadpass personal information practices are governed by this Privacy Policy. Please review it before making any use of our Site and Services.

By using the Services you also agree to this privacy statement. You acknowledge that (a) we cannot ensure the security or privacy of information you provide through the Internet and your email messages, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the use of such information by other parties; (b) we are not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information which you provide to them and you should use caution in selecting the personal information you provide to others through the service; and (c) we cannot assume any responsibility for the content of messages sent by other users of the service, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the contents of any communications you may receive from other users. We cannot guarantee, and assume no responsibility for verifying, the accuracy of the information provided by other users of the service.

You provide us, during the registration process and use of the Service, with two types of information personal information such as name, address, e-mail address and e-mails, and any other personal information, and billing information such as credit card number.

When you use the Service and/or log on to the Site, we may collect and receive your browser information, including IP address, "cookies" information [email name IP address coocie].

Your billing information is collected and transmitted to a secure payment processor until your account has been canceled, for the purpose of insuring you obligations with respect to the Service and the Site. Such connection with secure payment processors shall not create any responsibility or liability upon Roadpass with respect to any of the services provided by the secure payment processor, and you hereby wave any and all claims and causes of action against Roadpass in connections of such services. Please contact our secure payment processor so you may learn more about its privacy policies and level of data security,

Should you cancel the Service, your billing information will be removed by Roadpass and the secure payment processor company.

We may provide your personal information to third parties since our Service is also supplied by third parties. Please note that these third parties may have a different privacy policy.

As specified above, we may collect certain information about you and your web usage, which may be shared with third parties and used for advertising. NOTE: OUR SOFTWARE AND OTHER SERVICES COLLECT AND STORES INFORMATION CONCERNING YOUR ACTIVITY ON THE WEB, SUCH AS YOUR IP ADDRESS. IN SOME CASES, INFORMATION COLLECTED BY OUR SERVICES MAY BE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AND IN SOME CASES INFORMATION (INCLUDING INFORMATION FROM OR ABOUT PAGES OF SOCIAL MEDIA WEBSITES YOU VISIT) MAY BE USED OR SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR PURPOSES OF DISPLAYING TARGETED ADVERTISEMENTS PROMOTIONAL AND MARKETING MATERIAL TO YOU.

We may also release your information when we believe that such release is necessary in order to: (a) protect or defend any of our legal rights (including enforcement of agreements that we have interest in) or property, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors; (b) comply with applicable law, legal process or enforce our site policies. (c) Protect the safety and security of users of our Site and any of our Services or members of the public; or (d) protect against fraud or carry out our risk management procedures.

### External Links

This Site may contain links to or references to third party websites. These third parties may collect information about you as well. No endorsement or representation is hereby made in connection with any third party products, services or information or privacy practices. You should contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. You hereby wave any and all claims and causes of action against us in connections of such third parties content and privacy policies.

### Unsolicited Submission Policy

Roadpass does not accept, by any means of transmission, any unsolicited submissions, in any form whatsoever including, without limitation, any marketing, advertising and/or creative suggestions, scripts, lyrics, jingles, product samples, prototypes, movies and/or games (hereinafter referred to as "Submissions"). If you elect to forward to us any such Submission, then by doing so, you acknowledge that said Submission has not been requested by us and that (1) we are not liable for any use, disclosure, or return to you of your Submission, (2) no confidential relationship is established or is to be implied in any way from our receipt of the Submission and any statement to the contrary with your Submission shall not alter this condition, (3) you understand that you will not be entitled to any compensation from us based upon your Submission, (4) the receipt of your Submission shall not constitute a waiver by us of our rights to contest the validity of any copyright, or other intellectual property rights that you may now or hereafter claim for the Submission, and (5) any previously, concurrently or subsequently submitted materials relating to this Submission shall be considered to have been submitted in accordance with these conditions.

### Modifications

Roadpass Ltd. reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Such modifications shall be in full force and effect immediately upon publication. Notification of changes in this Privacy Policy will be posted on the Service/ Site (as defined in the Terms and Conditions) or sent via electronic mail, as we may determine in our sole discretion. If you do not agree to any modifications, you should terminate your use of the service immediately upon the publications of such change. Your continued use of the service now, or following the posting of notice of any changes in this Privacy Policy, will constitute a binding acceptance by you of this Privacy Policy, or any subsequent modifications.

### Disclosure and communication

We reserve the right to send electronic mail to you, for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to the service, or of any service's related products and services. We reserve the right to disclose information about your usage of the service and demographics in forms that do not reveal your personal identity.

### Managing Your Password and Your Account

You are solely responsible for managing your password and for keeping your password confidential. No one from Roadpass will be authorized to provide your password. If you have forgotten your password, click on the "Forgot Password?" link at the top of the screen. Follow the instructions, and a link to change your password will be emailed to you. You are also solely responsible for restricting access to any computer you use to access your account. You agree that you are responsible for all activities that occur on your account or through use of your password by yourself or by other persons.

### "RSS" Feeds

RSS feeds may be provided as a quick and easy way for you to distribute information from the web site or from your online account. RSS feeds are accessible through an XML-based URL that can be accessed with an RSS reader of your choice. Use of personal RSS feeds that contain information about your account (for example, Movie Ratings and Rental Activity features, if provided) is at your own discretion. If you use personal RSS feeds, you consent that the information in the feeds will be transferred to the location in which you enable the RSS feed. Roadpass will not pass any personally identifiable information in your feed. However, your use of an RSS feed may cause personally identifiable information that is associated with the RSS feed to be associated with you. You acknowledge that your use of an RSS feed and any personally identifiable information associated with it is at your sole discretion and risk.

Use of the service's RSS feeds is for non-commercial, personal use and whether or not you use an RSS feed is entirely at your discretion. You may not modify the RSS feeds. If an RSS feed contains an attribution to the service, you may not remove the attribution. Roadpass provides no warranty regarding its RSS feeds and reserves the right to terminate or modify the feeds at any time without notice. Roadpass is not responsible for any loss or damage incurred by you or anyone else due to your use of an RSS feed.

### Access to Your Online Account

If you opt for the "Remember me" feature for your online account, a cookie helps for online recall certain items of your specific information on subsequent visits, including your user name and password. When you return to (the service) Online, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so that it is not necessary to enter your user name and password to access certain functionality. While cookies are a convenience, please remember that if you elect the "Remember Me" option, anyone who can access the computer you are using will have the ability to access your account for certain functions and view certain information about your account, including viewing and making changes to your rental queue (if provided as a feature). Certain functions, such as accessing your complete Payment Card information, cannot be viewed through the use of cookies.

### Language

You agree that this Privacy Policy, the Site and the Service and all communications with Roadpass shall be in the English language.

### Entire Agreement

You agree that this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and Roadpass with respect to your use of this Site and the Service and supersede all previous agreements, understandings and representations relating thereto.
